[
 {
   "question_no":"1",
   "question":"What is 5+4-1?",
   "a":"10",
   "b":"2",
   "c":"8",
   "d":"9",
   "correct_ans":"c" 
 },
 {
    "question_no":"2",
   "question":"What is 9*2?",
   "a":"19",
   "b":"21",
   "c":"82",
   "d":"18",
   "correct_ans":"d" 
 },
 {
    "question_no":"3",
   "question":"What is 12-0?",
   "a":"12",
   "b":"2",
   "c":"8",
   "d":"18",
   "correct_ans":"a" 
 },
 {
    "question_no":"4",
   "question":"What is 8/2?",
   "a":"1",
   "b":"11",
   "c":"4",
   "d":"8",
   "correct_ans":"c" 
 },
 {
    "question_no":"5",
   "question":"What is 88*1?",
   "a":"14",
   "b":"88",
   "c":"99",
   "d":"22",
   "correct_ans":"b" 
 },
 {
    "question_no":"6",
   "question":"What is the next prime number after 5?",
   "a":"11",
   "b":"21",
   "c":"7",
   "d":"9",
   "correct_ans":"c" 
 },   
 {
    "question_no":"7",
   "question":"What is the value of 2 to the power of 5?",
   "a":"32",
   "b":"21",
   "c":"43",
   "d":"54",
   "correct_ans":"a" 
 },
 {
    "question_no":"8",
   "question":"What is the sum of the angles in a triangle?",
   "a":"190",
   "b":"210",
   "c":"820",
   "d":"180",
   "correct_ans":"d" 
 },
 {
    "question_no":"9",
   "question":"110 divided by 10 is",
   "a":"11",
   "b":"12",
   "c":"81",
   "d":"23",
   "correct_ans":"a" 
 },
 {
    "question_no":"10",
   "question":"Find the sum of 130 + 125 + 191?",
   "a":"423",
   "b":"143",
   "c":"446",
   "d":"444",
   "correct_ans":"c" 
 }
]